(Their third morning in Thailand)
(Their lodging in Bangkok, 9:00 a.m.)
Hello.
(Won Ji wakes up first.)
Good morning.
I'm wearing the clothes
my Secret Santa got me yesterday.
They were too long,
so I cut off about a hand's length.
It looks good, right?
(Ta-da)
I'm wearing pink today.
Everyone is passed out right now.
I should go wake them up.
They're up!
Hello.
Hi. Good morning.
Good morning.
(The queen shows up looking groggy.)
She's up.
What about upstairs?
I was about to check.
Peek-a-boo.
Are you up?
Good morning!
Good morning.
- You're wearing the pants I got you.
- I am.
I shortened them. What do you think?
You did! Good job.
- It looks good, right?
- Nice.
Cut what?
The pants.
(Impressed)
That's cute!
(She's in a good mood as always.)
I have nothing to do in the morning.
I got bored, so I altered my pants.
I showered too.
(Fitting)
I'm hungry.
Should I use it as a headband?
What if you wear it as a top?
This?
(The it girl is creative.)
This could be a headband.
(This might be good as a headband.)
(Exclaiming)
Doesn't it look
like an actual headband like this?
Yes, like a set.
It really looks like a headband.
(Loving it)
This seems like it would
tear pretty easily.
(Giggling)
It's really breathable.
Do you want me to read your fortune today?
- Sounds good.
- I do.
There's a website that I like.
What is it?
- Naver fortune.
- Naver fortune?
Really?
What should I tell you?
Your birthday and birth year.
(Typing)
Today's overall fortune!
"Joyful!"
Knock knocking a door
(Overwhelmed)
- Joyful.
- That's good.
Today is the day...
(Knocking)
Sim Cheong meets the Dragon King.
Oh, my goodness!
"Things keep getting in the way..."
"Things keep getting in the way
more than expected,"
"and you keep messing up
because you're all over the place."
What is that?
You said it was joyful.
Did it mean "discouraged"
instead of "joyful?"
I like that. I'm excited to start my day.
Hye Rim's overall fortune today.
"Prepare ahead."
- "Prepare ahead."
- Liu Bei and Zhang Fei.
Let's go, "Romance of the Three Kingdoms."
(Flustered)
Yours is "Prepare ahead."
Gabee too.
"Prepare ahead" for me too.
(Cheering)
We're Liu Bei and Zhang Fei!
We're the "Romance
of the Three Kingdoms" girls.
By the way, I did some research.
On what?
In Thailand...
No way!
Saju?
It's like astrology.
(It's like astrology.)
I love that!
There's a really famous place here.
It's super famous.
Thailand has its own form
of fortune-telling like saju.
(She looked
up traditional Thai astrology.)
It's a really famous place.
- Do you want to check it out?
- Let's go!
I love that idea.
Isn't it great?
Let's see how compatible we are!
There are a lot of ghosts in Thailand too.
- That's fascinating.
- Their readings might be accurate.
I know.
And nearby,
there's a talisman market.
- Talisman?
- A talisman market?
They sell...
- Superstitious items?
- little superstitious items there.
- I like that.
- I love that!
Let's have some fun there!
- Let's have fun!
It's going to be so much fun!
Let's have fun!
(Promising to have fun)
Let's have a lot of fun.
I think we've gotten pretty close.
Sian is less shy now.
You don't have to worry about those two.
I've changed a lot too.
I'm excited about today.
I'm looking forward to it.
- I'll go change.
- Take your time.
I'll bring some pants.
If this pair rips, I'll wear this.
This? I need some hiking pants.
Can I put in our towels?
Yes. If you have some towels
on the third floor, bring them with you.
Let me look up a laundromat.
There's one.
Three minutes away on foot.
(Finds where the laundromat is)
It's super close.
Why is your bag so big?
It's a laundry basket.
A laundry basket.
(The laundry basket was in the lodging.)
We have 2,160 baht left.
- Our shared money?
- Yes.
(They have about 100 dollars left.)
We spent a lot yesterday...
- We did.
- since we went pretty far.
(Cheering)
(The brush appears today too.)
Come on.
Thank you.
That's 4,000, 5,000, 6,000.
Shall we contribute 1,000 baht each?
Okay.
It's 1,000 each.
Let's do the laundry and go eat.
- Let's get something to drink too.
- Okay.
Let's go.
We just go straight. Hello.
Hello.
(Starting their day with greetings)
Good morning.
- It's nice.
- It's really nice.
The weather is nice today.
It's pretty nice.
(The perfect weather to do laundry)
And we turn left here.
Look at that.
Hello.
He has a lot of flowers on him.
Did you notice...
that they all have shrines
in front of their houses?
- Did you see that?
- I did.
- There are so many.
- I know.
Every house has one.
There it is. "Enjoy Laundry."
- It looks nice.
- It's hip.
This one is for 18kg,
and this one is for 13kg.
We could split the laundry
between two 13kg machines...
and one 18-kg machine.
How much would it be?
It's 60 baht.
- It's 60 baht.
- It's 100 baht.
- It's about 300 baht.
- That should be more than enough.
If you put them in,
it will recognize them automatically.
Is that so?
(Inserting)
- I'll take them out.
- Okay.
(Exchanging for coins)
These 2 are detergent,
and these 2 are fabric softener.
- We need three, at least.
- Right.
Our laundry is pretty dirty.
And let's buy enough fabric softener.
- This!
- This?
(Buying what Sian wants)
One.
Let's wash...
towels and underwear first.
Then, let's wash the clothes together.
Let me put some here too.
(While Won Ji and Sian are putting
their laundry in the washers,)
(Gabee puts the coins in.)
(Inserting)
It's going smoothly.
It says "36 minutes."
Shall we eat after putting them
in the dryers?
- We forgot about this! Wait!
- We forgot about this.
(Left on the table)
Hold on.
(Rushing)
Which one has more laundry?
Let's put it in the one for outerwear.
I can't open it.
(The treasurer with long nails
is also on it.)
(They managed to take care of it!)
Okay!
Done.
- Okay.
- We got it.
There's a five-star place.
There's a good place 300m away.
Let's go there.
There's a noodle place this way.
I love noodles.
Here!
We're here.
This one is open.
It's a Michelin restaurant.
A Michelin restaurant?
A Michelin-starred restaurant.
(Just down the alley,)
(there's a Michelin-star restaurant.)
(A lot of locals come here too.)
(Just seeing the ingredients
at the entrance gets you excited.)
It's been a Michelin restaurant
since 2019.
That's true.
(Thumbs-up)
So in total,
- Amazing!
- it's been eight years.
It smells so good.
(Taking their seats, feeling excited)
This looks good. I love this one.
Meat soup?
(Different kinds of Thai meat soups)
A soup?
This one?
I want this with soup.
I want this too.
One beef noodles without soup.
Two beef soups.
One meatball soup.
I have a feeling this place will be good.
- I agree.
- I know.
(Pouring the hot broth over the meat
to warm it through)
(Topping it
with a variety of garnishes...)
(and finishing it with their secret sauce)
It came out quickly!
- My goodness.
- That looks so good.
- It reminds me of bun cha.
- It does.
That looks good.
It looks really good.
(Gabee and Harimu's beef soup)
It's like cold noodles
and spicy cold noodles.
(Beef soup and beef noodles)
Won Ji!
My favorite.
(Won Ji's meatball soup)
It looks delicious.
Nice!
- Okay!
- Yes!
Let's eat.
- Let's eat.
- It looks tasty.
Let me give it a taste.
Oh, my gosh.
Do you guys have noodles?
- You don't?
- I don't have noodles.
- What?
- You don't have noodles?
You guys don't have noodles either?
- Why don't we?
- You're right.
(Sian is the only one who has noodles.)
- Shall we ask for noodles?
- Yes.
Excuse me.
Could you please add noodles?
- Noodles?
- Yes.
No noodles?
Really?
Then can I...
Can I order this?
One more of this.
Like this?
There's no meat.
Why did she just give you noodles?
I kept asking for noodles,
so that's all I got.
(Starting with a spoonful of broth)
What's this?
Bulgogi soup?
- This is a lot like short rib soup.
- It's exactly like short rib soup.
(Rich, meaty, short rib soup-like broth)
(Straight to a bite of meat)
(One bite after another)
(Savoring the flavor)
This meat is like...
short rib soup meat with the bone removed.
- The bone.
- So it's tender.
It's so tender it practically melts.
Agreed. The meat is delicious.
Let's try it. Try this.
(Sliding it over)
(She's giving her meat.)
- Aren't you giving me all of it?
- Giving Won Ji all her love.
Then you should try this.
It's kind of like a fish cake with meat.
(Big bite)
- Isn't it incredibly bouncy?
- Totally.
This one's very bouncy and a bit salty.
- Try them together.
- Okay.
(Big bite)
(Savoring the flavor)
- It tastes completely packed with meat.
- Right?
The umami builds as you chew.
It's an interesting flavor.
(Slurping)
But it's really good.
(Now a bite of beef noodles)
(Savoring the flavor)
(Puzzled by the flavor)
(Won Ji takes a bite too.)
How are the noodles? Interesting, right?
- You like firm noodles.
- Totally.
These noodles are extremely firm.
They're very firm and chewy.
Firm and chewy.
This place is good.
(Dipping)
(Now dipping it in the sauce)
This sauce is good.
How is it? The sauce is the star.
- The sauce makes the dish.
- It really does.
Exactly.
Southeast Asian food uses
lots of fish sauce.
- That's why it all has this tangy flavor.
- Yes, right.
- You like Thai food now, don't you?
- Absolutely.
Let's eat at Thai restaurants
back in Korea.
- Sounds great.
- Right?
Let's plan what to ask
at the fortune reading too.
(Questions before the astrology reading)
What's everyone's biggest concern lately?
My biggest concern?
First, whether this show will
work out well.
Health.
Maybe they're best at predicting marriage.
Or what kind of work suits you.
- Good.
- I'm curious.
(Strongly agrees)
Should I ask which job suits me?
I've been worried about my future lately.
Have you all had your fortune told
or had a saju reading before?
Of course.
I've never gone for a proper saju reading,
but a close friend of mine became
a shaman.
(Intrigued and shocked)
That's fascinating.
Almost everything she tells me comes true.
What did she say?
She said I'd want more
than just college...
and would start working very early.
She told me things like that.
What about you?
I've had several readings.
I said I want to lead
a fairly ordinary life.
They say I can't.
(A born star)
I'm not a star. It's more like...
You can think of it
all as hits of dopamine.
Deep down, our highs and lows are intense.
What if we end up sobbing at the reading?
I'm finished.
It's 760 baht.
That was good.
(Thank you for the meal.)
There's a cafe over there too.
There's a cafe?
Let's run the dryer and go.
Sounds good.
We're here.
- We made it.
(Back at the laundromat)
It smells good.
(The clothes are clean now.)
(Checking the dryer)
It's clean in here.
They maintain it well.
(Loading the dryer)
That's plenty.
This seems like the high heat setting.
- High heat?
- Sure.
(Paying 60 baht,
about 2 dollars and 80 cents)
We're a great team.
How many minutes will it take?
It will take 40 minutes.
- Great.
- That's perfect.
Let's find a cafe.
There's one down this alley.
It looks cool in there.
- That looks good.
- Coffee.
It's pretty.
- Shall we go?
- Let's go.
Nice.
I'm going to buy two drinks.
Nice!
Ostrich! Ostrich!
Ostrich!
- Go straight!
- Straight ahead.
Go straight!
Is this a convex mirror?
Let's take a picture here.
A picture!
(A feel-good selfie)
We look so cute!
Okay.
(Cute even when distorted)
Let's go.
Are we almost there?
- Turn left here.
- It's so hot.
I like this alley.
(Entering a charming cafe alley)
Over there.
- I see.
- Okay.
There seem to be lots of travelers here.
They sell matcha too.
- Great.
- Matcha.
I'll have three drinks.
You clearly found a great cafe.
The air conditioning looks really strong.
- This place has a Seongsu vibe.
- It does.
- Hello.
Let's order.
Should I pay for this with my own money?
- You're having two drinks, right?
- Yes.
I can't buy two with our shared money.
We caught you.
One Thai tea and one iced Americano.
Only two, please.
Strawberry matcha sounds good too.
The mixed berry smoothie looks good.
The chocolate milkshake looks good.
- These two?
- Yes.
Then I'll order this one.
One strawberry matcha
and one long black iced coffee.
One mixed berry smoothie
and one chocolate milkshake.
And a strawberry cream croissant.
I always need dessert after a meal.
(Their huge cafe order is complete.)
- Many people retire and move here.
- Right.
(Hopping)
Look at you.
(The neighborhood boss appears.)
Hi, kitty.
- This cat is so friendly.
- Its paws are tiny.
It looks like a baby.
(Clacking)
(Harimu's multipurpose nails)
What is this?
No, you can't have this.
You can't have this.
Look, it's settled in.
(A seat fit for the local boss)
What's with you?
We meet so many animals.
We have good luck with animals.
A dog yesterday and a cat today.
(Who's next?)
I think 40 minutes will pass quickly.
We're in trouble.
It's probably been 15 minutes.
Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
One person does it all.
- Sure.
- Great.
It's seriously hot.
This might be the hottest day.
Day Three is the hottest so far.
It's too hot.
- Now?
- Yes.
The loser takes this and goes back.
The loser has to run there after we play.
We need time to prepare ourselves.
Okay, rock-paper-scissors.
Rock-paper-scissors.
Nice! Rock-paper-scissors.
(Joy and sorrow)
Thank you! Thank you!
You love me! I love you, too!
(A sudden profession of faith)
(Impressive)
Rock-paper-scissors, shoot!
(Sian is going to the laundromat.)
Thank you! You see me. I see you.
(A successful conversion)
(Springing up)
Her true feelings? That's amazing!
She's going. She's off.
It's insanely hot.
I just ordered three desserts,
so we could all share them.
(Feeling wronged)
I honestly didn't think I'd lose.
(You should've won.)
What were the chances it'd be me?
(The drinks are ready in the meantime.)
(We each ordered two drinks.)
(Four people and seven cups)
I'm so happy.
I'm usually the only one ordering
two drinks.
I'm excited that you're matching
my energy.
I ordered the strawberry matcha.
Strawberry matcha.
You can see the strawberry down there.
Right?
Try a sip.
Matcha, matcha, ya-ya
(Eyes widening)
She's really trying.
You sang, "Matcha, matcha, ya ya."
We have to play along.
Gitchi gitchi ya ya da da
Try this too.
Did you order it for us to share?
I did. Help yourself.
- Want me to cut it?
- Yes, please.
(Slicing)
Now it's a mess.
Go ahead. It all looks the same
in your stomach.
(Nibbling)
Good choice. This makes me happy.
The cream is delicious.
(Whirring)
(Suddenly imitating a blender)
She's doing an astrology reading now.
She's reading our fortunes.
(Playing coy)
How does today look?
It looks promising.
(Dying of laughter)
I think it'll go smoothly.
That's all I need.
I thought I took this out of my suitcase.
- Really?
- Who put it back?
- You're wearing it?
- Who did?
- I took it out.
- I didn't put it back.
- You too?
- Her?
I put it in.
I did.
I put it in, but...
This is why I packed it.
We might have a military experience.
I could wear it while crawling
on the ground.
A top while crawling on the ground?
It'd probably fall apart while you crawl.
A combat-crawling top.
The military top has returned alive.
On a two-week trip,
not exaggerating,
I literally bring 40 to 50 tops,
then buy ten more on the trip.
For me, tops are
more important than bottoms.
Yes, you've been wearing the same pants
for three days in a row.
I'm keeping these pants on for two weeks.
Time flies. It's already been 46 minutes.
We have four minutes left.
(Oh right.)
I forgot about that.
Let's go get our laundry.
- Okay.
- Good luck!
- You got this!
(Wait)
I'll go with Sian.
It's going to be a date.
Wow.
Are you going together?
Yes.
- The two of you?
- Yes.
We'll be back.
(Harimu joins in.)
We'll be quick.
Good luck!
Cover yourself.
(Singing)
What if it rains?
Oh my!
(Singing)
(Sound effects)
Music brings us together.
I think it's done, right?
I think so.
(Third time visiting the laundromat)
It's finished.
Let's open it.
Is it fluffy?
Very!
It smells so good.
- Thanks for coming with me.
- No problem, roommate.
Best friends forever.
We were each other's Secret Santas.
Off we go.
What do you think of our friendship?
(We're best friends.)
Let's go.
This would have been
too heavy for one person.
Yes, this is a bit heavy.
Why is it heavier after laundry?
It wasn't this heavy in the morning.
Okay guys, we're back.
(Back at the hotel)
Hi!
Oh, it's so cool and nice.
Thank you.
We still have to take them out,
otherwise it's going to get all damp.
They're really warm.
They're so clean.
Let's do it again.
All right.
Let's spread them out a bit
before leaving.
Okay.
I'll call the taxi.
All right.
Let's get the taxi and go.
Let's go!
- It's only 10 minutes away.
- Yes!
(10 minutes to the fortune teller)
Oh, the taxi's here.
- Okay, let's go!
- The taxi is here.
I'm so excited.
Let's go, Day Three!
(Day 3 officially begins.)
Is that it?
- Is that our taxi, Gabee?
- That's it.
Yes, it's that one.
I'll sit in the middle, Harimu.
No, I will.
- I'll sit in the middle.
- Get in the middle.
(Being considerate)
Hello!
Hello.
Are you okay back there?
It's only a short ride.
(Heading off to the fortune teller)
(Singing)
Let's ride a taxi...
and go over there.
(Not used to the lively vibe)
(Excitedly heading to downtown Bangkok)
Thailand is great.
(Heading to Tha Pra Chan)
Oh, an unfamiliar path.
Jewelry?
- Jewelry?
- Jewelry.
They're like a jukebox.
(Singing)
(Dancing)
(An introvert internally screaming)
Check out those details.
This was the first song I performed
on stage.
- Seriously?
- When I was five.
That song gave me a taste of the stage.
You were just five?
You were only five back then?
Thank you, Jewelry!
I also have a first performance story.
Really?
- Can you guess what it was?
- Show me.
I love my boy
(Diva by After School)
(Singing along)
(Clapping)
(Please, send help.)
So you all performed on stage
when you were young.
Mine was when I was in 5th grade...
at a senior center.
- The senior center!
- We went volunteering...
and four of us danced.
What about you, Won Ji?
I've never been on stage before.
(A 100 percent introvert
with no stage experience)
What's going to be your debut song?
What should it be?
I pick "Bromm, Taki."
Your debut stage is going
to be "Bromm, Taki?"
- Of course.
- I'm so honored.
Bromm, Taki
(Giggling)
(The world's flattest debut)
Won Ji.
It's like you're meditating.
Bromm, Taki!
(A dance track turned solemn)
Let's do a debut stage!
My debut is today!
- That's funny.
- Yesterday, I heard a toad.
(Gabee's toad?)
Really?
It must've been a real toad...
because we didn't use it yesterday.
We didn't.
Really?
- Did you hear it?
- No.
But I heard it.
Thailand has many ghosts.
I never touched it once yesterday.
- No way.
- Seriously.
I definitely heard it.
We left it downstairs.
So we never got to use it.
We left it in the bag.
- They left it downstairs.
- I really heard it.
- It's a ghost toad!
- So I thought...
you were cute for using it...
and that it sounded nice.
That was a ghost.
(What did Sian hear?)
- Here we are.
- Is this the place?
(The taxi arrives at the destination.)
They even have fortune-telling merch here.
- Really?
- Wow.
Cool!
Thank you!
Thank you.
Have a nice day.
This is the place.
They're selling frame keychains.
They have a lot of photo frame things.
I want something...
- like that.
- That looks like a necklace.
- Is this a fortune teller's street?
- All of these.
The whole street is like that.
I guess so.
- They have amulets.
- Right, they have talismans.
They even have herbal inhalers.
(Street full of amulets and merch)
There are so many.
Keep going.
Yes, keep going.
This place feels more urban.
Yes, it does.
Follow me.
(Peaceful and quiet Tha Phra Chan)
In Thailand, you should never...
touch a monk.
- Really?
- Never.
Never.
This place doesn't have any cars.
The flowers are so pretty.
(Entering a car-free zone)
Let's go slowly, girls.
Slay.
(Slow down and look around.)
- Slow down, girls.
- Slow.
(Taking in the feedback with her body)
Oh, tacos!
They sell tacos.
- The specialty coffee looks nice!
- Right!
That place looks classy, too.
That place looks good.
Is it over there?
Yes, let's keep moving.
Phra Chan.
Tha Phra Chan.
(A riverside complex filled
with shops and eateries)
(A popular tourist spot known
for astrology and fortune telling)
(A pier located
along the Chao Phraya River)
(Bursting with food, shops,
and fortune tellers)
(Connected to a 100-year-old
traditional amulet market)
We're not getting on a boat.
(Entering the building)
Is it inside here?
This looks like a shopping arcade.
It kind of looks like a station.
This place has an interesting vibe.
They sell records there.
You can see a river over there.
Finally, we're seeing the river.
This way. Have a look.
(Taking in the view)
Hi.
Wow, water hyacinths!
This place has a lot of them.
- This is a fortune-telling zone.
- This way.
So this is the place.
Hello.
(Arrives at the fortune teller)
- Shall we sit?
- What about chairs?
Hello.
You two can sit here.
(Taking seats right away)
Two can sit there.
We need to talk to her, though.
(Taking the innermost seats)
Just a second.
We have a translator app here.
I'm on it. "We want..."
"our Thai astrology reading done."
- Hello.
- Hello!
Hello.
Tell her that we want our fortunes told.
(Translator ready)
We're here for Thai fortune telling.
Tell me your birthdate.
She wants to know our birthdate.
My birthdate is...
(First conversation: success)
Let's write it down.
Yes, let's write it down for her.
And let's send the message.
First, second, third, and fourth.
I'm the first one.
Number Won Ji.
(Kindly laughing at the dad joke)
Do tourists get their fortune told...
when they visit Korea?
It might be hard
with the language barrier.
I don't think many would
even think about it.
- Wow.
- Gosh!
She's using a book.
What is that?
It's full of numbers.
(Wall of numbers)
She looks so serious.
Very serious.
(Focused)
She's writing down all the numbers.
She's calculating something.
(She writes something.)
There's one at every interval
like a clock.
Right. I can see the zodiac signs.
In Thai astrology,
there's a guardian deity
for each day of the week,
and not just your birthday and year.
It's kind of like a mix
of saju and astrology.
It's totally different from Korea.
- We use Chinese characters for that.
- That's right.
I guess they even offer yogurt drinks
to the gods.
Seems like it.
I thought it was Korean one.
It's water with a straw in it.
You're right.
Hello. It's nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you.
(Suddenly)
(The fortune teller finishes the reading.)
I'm nervous.
It's making me nervous.
Let's reveal the results!
What if it says that I'm doomed?
No way.
Based on your face reading,
you're not bound to fail.
Because you're a born cutie!
I've never heard of that before.
A born cutie.
(Powered by cuteness)
As for your personality,
you're naturally quiet...
and a bit impatient.
Didn't we agree not to do that?
Oh, right. I forgot.
Just kidding. You do what you want.
How did she know I'm impatient?
I'm seriously in the top one percent
when it comes to being impatient.
I may seem calm,
but I'm actually really impatient.
- I need things done quickly.
- You need to do a lot too.
Everything should be done "ASAP."
I think I get what you mean.
You have a knack for business
and making money.
So,
money will keep flowing your way.
- Make money, girl!
- Money, money.
Money!
But never co-sign for anyone.
You'll end up shouldering
all the responsibility.
Co-sign!
(Just the fortune teller's
personal opinion.)
- No co-signing.
- Never.
(Never co-sign!)
According to your reading,
(Focused)
you're destined to meet your soulmate.
(Indistinct speech)
I feel like she's saying something huge.
Your friend's friend likes you.
My friend's friend has a crush on me?
This is true.
A mutual friend!
- It's true, right?
- A mutual friend.
- That's how you two met!
- That's right.
You're amazing, sis!
You're so good at this!
(This lady knows what she's doing.)
(Next up is Gabee!)
You'll have a lot of expenses
over the next two months.
For the next two?
Guess you'll be spending a lot.
And I see a change in where you live.
It looks like you'll be moving.
Is this true?
- Are you serious?
- This just gave me chills.
- When?
- Next year.
I've already signed the contract
for my new place next year.
Really?
It's basically a done deal.
I'm moving next year.
I signed the contract in advance.
(Spot on.)
First of all,
you have very high self-esteem.
And you're very stubborn.
Stubborn, she says.
Miss. Stubborn.
She seems pretty certain.
This is true.
Impatient and stubborn.
But you need to be stubborn sometimes.
It's definitely needed.
It's a dangerous world out there.
You need some stubbornness.
As for your career,
good fortune is coming your way
starting this year.
And it'll last for the next ten years.
(Jackpot)
- Ten years.
Wow, ten years.
- That's good.
- And as for love,
you'll meet your destined partner
this year.
If someone comes along,
you have to open your heart.
Three will come. Choose wisely.
- Three?
- Three guys?
(Not one, not two, but three men!)
- Meow!
- Meow! Meow!
- Who are you going to choose?
- Catch!
Who's going to be mine?
- Thank you.
(Much appreciated)
(It's Sian's turn now.)
(Nervous)
You're the one putting gold
on the back of the Buddha statue.
You're someone who does good
behind the scenes without seeking credit.
Even when you do good deeds,
no one knows about them.
(Emotional)
- We'll know.
- For sure. Don't worry.
But that would really suck.
It's not fair.
You're good at making money, too.
You love your family,
and you'd do anything for them.
Amazing daughter.
(She will be a rich and nice daughter.)
Right now, you're in a period
where money comes easily.
And that begins...
this year. You're destined
to become very wealthy.
Everything's working out for everyone!
It's really working out
for the three of us!
- Yes.
- I'm so glad.
But even in Korea,
they said my luck is just getting started.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Looks like you picked a winner, Producer.
You really made the perfect choice.
I also see a lot of people
who'll help you.
You'll have supportive coworkers,
and you'll meet a lot of people
who'll help you along the way.
A lot of benefactors, she says!
- Benefactor 1, 2, 3!
- Benefactors!
(I've already met benefactors!)
Benefactors? To queens!
- Queens!
(With benefactors, they are now queens.)
Thank you.
- At last.
- That look of "Finally, it's you."
"Finally it's you?"
Let's get this loud one over with.
People born with this fate...
tend to be very straightforward
with their words.
The moment they know it's not right,
they walk away.
This is true.
It's obvious what you like and don't like.
- That's right.
- You either love it or hate it.
You're a strong and adventurous type.
You're bold, courageous,
and someone people can always rely on.
- She's right.
- Like manly?
Yes.
I'm a warrior at heart!
Yeah, I hear that a lot.
You've probably been making
a lot of money since last February.
Your career has a lot of good things
in store for you.
And this will last...
for the next eleven years.
Okay.
- We're all so lucky.
- Yes, sir.
(All four of them have good luck.)
(She can't help but dance.)
Thank you.
Let's look at our compatibility,
and do a tarot reading.
- Compatibility reading. Let's go!
- Let's go.
It's been forever
since I had a tarot reading.
I don't even remember when I had one.
(Pick a card each.)
- One.
- At once.
- Okay.
- Let's pick together.
- Alright.
I'm going to pick...
In 1, 2, 3.
(Choosing carefully)
This one.
I'm so excited!
Our compatibility!
(Nervous)
Even more nerve-racking
than the personal readings.
(The cards are revealed one by one.)
(Harimu, Sian, Gabee, Won Ji)
This person is good at what she does,
but she's especially good with money.
You're the money manager!
(Born to handle the money?)
You're our money manager.
The second card represents someone
who gets along with everyone.
You naturally fit in
and bring harmony to the group.
Yeah, definitely.
- A peacemaker.
- The one who holds us together.
(So far, the four of them are
getting along perfectly.)
(Expecting good word)
The third person...
complains a lot.
(Oops.)
She's picking up mine too.
(Dizzy)
But this person keeps everyone grounded.
So I'm the problem.
I'm the problem.
- Not at all!
- No way.
- There are zero problems.
- We're just different.
I'm the problem.
You may work together,
but you'll grow into close friends.
you'll be loving friends.
We'll become friends
who truly care about each other.
This is so true. You're right.
I just need to keep my mouth shut.
- No way.
- Come on!
She's not like that!
I think it's good advice.
- Being too straightforward can be...
- No, I'm the impatient one.
We will keep our mouths shut.
Zip.
Then nothing will work.
You're good.
You can keep traveling together.
Thank you.
Alright. We're a good combo!
We're all good personally.
But I want to know
if our show's going to go big.
She said we'll go big.
Dang! She said it three times!
- She said "Dang."
- Dang! Dang! Dang!
It means it will become famous.
- You mean we'll make it big?
- Fame.
So we're going to take the world by storm?
Okay.
- I'm so happy.
- This is great.
Thank you.
We are compatible.
- I knew we'd be a good team.
- Sure.
It was so obvious!
Of course. We felt it all along.
(After the interesting astrology reading)
Was there anything that felt
especially accurate?
Wherever I go,
they always tell me I'm impatient.
I guess it's just the way I am.
They always say my face gives me away.
I'm always told that I'm stubborn, too.
Maybe I look like it?
They always tell me...
- You're fickle?
- Yes, fickle.
I'm so happy she said we're a good match.
That's all that matters!
That's what matters most.
I heard they have...
a talisman shop here.
Yeah, they have one here.
It's close by.
Let me guide you the way to the shop.
I think this is the entrance.
That's right. It begins here.
Here we go.
(There is a strange vibe in the alley.)
- But this is kind of scary.
- Exactly.
Look at this.
Don't be afraid.
- These things will protect you.
- Really?
It's a skull.
(Such a creepy-looking item)
There's something
in what looks like blood.
(An assortment
of creepy objects fills the stall)
- Is this ginseng?
- There's something.
It's too...
Everyone, look at this.
What do you think they are?
It looks like a goblin.
(Creepy)
(In awe)
(What is this place?)
I usually buy these kind of things
at a time,
but this feels way too serious.
- It feels way too serious, right?
- Exactly.
I want something I can carry every day.
- I want something cute.
- I hope they have something cute.
Like a key ring...
(Looking for a more
everyday kind of talisman)
There are so many shops here.
It's like Dongdaemun Market.
- There are so many Buddha statues
- Buddha merchandise.
They sell a lot of things
like necklace pendants.
Yes, there are so many pendants.
When I traveled around Thailand,
I saw so many people wearing pendants,
- about this size around their necks.
- Exactly.
(Thailand's amulet necklace culture)
(Thailand's amulet culture)
(Amulets are commonly worn as jewelry.)
(They carry spiritual
and religious significance.)
I guess you put the pendant in here.
I think so.
They sell these frame-like key ring cases.
I guess you can put
whatever you want inside.
(Customizable amulet necklaces)
This one is kind of cute.
Is this a Thai person?
Maybe he's a monk. They're so colorful.
I guess there are quite
a few famous monks here.
Yes, well-known monks.
Exactly.
There are a lot of well-known monks here.
- This is pretty.
- There are a lot of pretty ones here.
Is that so?
Isn't this one cute?
This one is totally my style.
It looks like Santa Claus.
You really do like
colorful things, Won Ji.
I like this too.
(Searching through the items)
There are so many
ridiculously suggestive ones.
It's like a nightlife show.
There are so many shameless individuals.
And this lady too.
(She keeps showing them to everyone.)
This would be heavy
to wear around your neck.
Yes.
I want to buy it,
but it's too heavy to carry.
- Let's look around a little more.
- Yes, let's go.
(Street stalls continue
through the maze-like alleys)
There are so many interesting things.
There are some here too.
They have things that look like coins.
Let's buy one here.
Okay.
There are so many cute ones.
Cute, right?
I like these old coins.
Me too.
Pretty good, right?
How about this one?
A coin?
- It feels like money will be flowing in.
- Right.
It's small enough
to carry around in your wallet.
Yes, it's small enough.
What does this coin mean?
It's 30 baht.
Does it mean 30 baht?
She says it means 30 baht.
It means 30 baht.
She said it's 30 baht.
And I think it probably
symbolizes financial luck.
I'll buy one for each of us four.
Won Ji is treating
everyone to lucky coins.
So that's 120 baht in total?
(They bought 5.6 dollars
worth of good luck)
The value is whatever we decide it is.
A talisman gets its power
from what you believe in.
It all comes from your own mind.
Let's go a little farther.
I think that's the end.
Let's go all the way to the end.
- Wait.
- Hold on.
There's a QR code here.
- Suddenly?
- All of a sudden?
(A suspicious QR code
appears in the amulet market.)
- This is crazy.
- This elephant plate is cute.
- Let's scan it right now.
- What's going on?
- What's this?
- It's a talisman.
All of a sudden?
What's this?
- What's this?
- Something popped up.
Really?
This is it.
It's an abandoned building.
This is so scary.
I'm scared.
(Frozen)
I really hate scary stuff.
It looks like a stopped escalator.
It has this old-fashioned vibe.
What if it's covered
in blood or something?
- It says it's a chance to find good luck.
- Seriously?
It tells us to go to a lucky place.
Seize your chance for good luck tonight.
Any luck you find there will be yours.
Is this some kind of treasure hunt?
Click here to go to the place of luck.
Find good luck?
This is totally high-tech.
- It says the place is closed down.
- Horror experience all of a sudden?
- I'm really scared.
- It says it's closed down.
I'm so scared.
Is this an abandoned-building experience?
(A gloomy atmosphere
surrounds this supposedly Lucky Place.)
It doesn't look very lucky to me.
(What kind of luck is here?)
(Not exactly thrilled)
It's closed down.
It says it's closed down.
It's not far from here.
Let's go check it out.
I'm a woman who went
to an abandoned building in Hong Kong.
Really?
"I'm a woman who went
to an abandoned building in Hong Kong."
Abandoned building in Hong Kong.
You went to the Himalayas too, didn't you?
She's been to the Himalayas and
an abandoned building in Hong Kong.
Let's check it out.
No, this is so scary.
I guess they have it.
Should I grab some coffee?
(They said they were going right away,
then suddenly changed course.)
Matcha and...
- Crepe.
- I want a crepe.
Can I have one banana chocolate crepe?
I need to eat a crepe
and build up my courage.
(Soothing her anxiety with dessert)
I'm going to get a Thai tea.
It looks good.
(Harimu also buys a cool, sweet dessert.)
Did they go get coffee?
(This is mine.)
(Meanwhile, the sisters are...)
(lost in their shopping spree.)
Are you buying all of that?
No, I'm not.
Can you help me pick something?
Sure.
Number one.
Number two.
Number three.
This one.
(Going with the blue one
the youngers recommended)
(Shaking her head)
(She secretly tries to bargain.)
Is there no discount?
I have no choice.
(When the negotiation fails,
her voice gets louder.)
I don't have much money.
(She tries to win sympathy,
even though they can't understand her.)
It's so pretty. It's totally my style.
(Spending 250 baht on peacock upkeep)
Oh, right. I ordered a crepe.
I need to pick up my crepe.
This one is cute too.
(She tends to lose all sense of reason
whenever she sees something cute.)
This is totally you.
It's totally mine.
(She immediately claims ownership.)
(It's 59 baht for one,
or 100 baht for two.)
How about 50 baht for one?
Okay.
I need to go pick up my crepe.
(There she came.)
It's done now.
- I came at exactly the right time.
- Yes.
- It took quite a while.
- Let's share this.
Let's sit down.
My pants ripped again.
Do you want to go change?
You brought a spare pair.
Right.
I knew this would happen,
so I brought another pair of pants.
Then I'll show off
the shirt I just bought too.
I'll be right back.
Doesn't she keep
twerking behind our backs?
(Not shaking, just covering)
(She was supposed to be right back.)
Buying something.
Since my pants ripped,
I changed into the shirt I bought earlier.
And she really likes this headscarf.
- Exactly.
- I'm good at getting people into things.
So I brought her over.
I want to copy your style.
You're such an it girl.
- I'm an it girl.
- You're an it girl.
What did you buy?
The one you recommended.
I like that.
I really wanted to try this.
Now is the perfect time.
Now is the time.
Because your outfit is way too plain.
It's too plain, right?
It's so plain that I'm not happy.
I've always loved scarves, so...
Isn't this pin so cute? Should I get one?
Isn't this one so cute?
It really is.
They're three for 100 baht.
It looks like you.
- It really is.
- Right?
This is totally me.
Even the round nose.
- This is totally you, Won Ji.
- I know.
But you never wear pins.
- No, I don't.
- I've never seen you wear one.
Pins don't suit me.
Then do you want to get
matching pins with me?
Matching pins?
Tempting.
Because my bangs keep falling down.
Really? They're three for 100 baht.
So, should we get this or this?
- Put it up against your hair.
- This one is ugly.
- The cherry one looks much better.
- Put this one back.
How about the strawberry one?
- But it's similar, right?
- This one is cute.
- What about this one?
- Which one?
That's pretty.
Okay.
I'm not really into it, but...
- What else is here?
- Isn't this one better?
What about this smiley one?
Isn't this one pretty?
(Well...)
- I don't think our tastes match well.
- Absolutely.
I don't think we can do a group buy.
Group buying?
Then how about we pick one for you?
- Great idea.
- Are there any other options?
- This one.
(The smiley pin
she couldn't quite let go of)
There's one more. This one too.
Not a chance.
I think we're just not compatible at all.
But that one is the best.
Is this one the best?
We've made our final decision.
The one I wanted...
Why things...
Let's smile a lot.
"Let's smile a lot" pin.
(Before we change our mind,
let's just pay for it.)
We bought our pins.
- Matching pins!
- Cute!
I'll put it on you.
- A cute couple!
- Okay.
- Should we put them on each other?
- Yes.
I'll put it here.
- Okay!
- That's cute.
- It's not bad.
- It looks good.
- It does?
Okay!
We spent money again.
- Cute!
- Adorable.
(Their suitcase slowly fills up
today too.)
I did some research.
The lucky place that we're visiting today.
It's a famous filming location
for Thai horror films.
Let's not do that.
There are a few ghost stories
about this place.
One says that after the theater
was abandoned,
people saw someone sitting alone
in the empty audience.
(Humming scary music)
What is she going to do alone?
So it's haunted.
People also have seen...
ghostly figures performing on the stage.
That doesn't make sense.
At night, the projector starts
playing movies on its own.
Who's turning that on?
A ghost!
(No way.)
They hear screams
coming from the audience.
That could be me.
They can hear someone whimper.
That's ridiculous.
- You've been to a haunted house.
- I have.
- In Hong Kong?
An abandoned school in Hong Kong.
How was it?
- It was so scary.
- I hate it.
The aura makes it impossible to go inside.
Did you see something?
I did.
What did you see?
I'm not sure.
But I did something.
- What was it?
- I felt some energy.
There were bats flying around.
- What?
I promised myself
I'd never go to a haunted place again.
Never ever.
Are you afraid of ghosts?
- I hate them.
- All three of you?
- I hate them so much.
At least one of us shouldn't.
(What are the four scaredy-cats going
to do there?)
- We need someone to lead us.
- I'll do it.
But Sian, it should be someone
who's good at it.
You said you hated ghosts.
- No. I'll do it.
- You said you hated them.
- You want to?
- I'll beat them up.
- Really?
- I'm quite strong.
- Okay.
- Are you sure?
I'll beat them all up.
That sounds good.
Sian is also taller than us.
Let's hide behind her.
- Yes. We should hide behind her.
- Just hide behind me.
(Why do I feel like it was a trap?)
That's good.
I'm scared.
I'm sure I'm the strongest among us.
Okay. Then let's get going.
Shall we go?
(Let's go check what our luck is.)
Which bus are we taking?
A green bus that says 60.
We're waiting for our bus.
There's a bus
that goes to the abandoned theater.
We don't have much money,
so we should take a bus.
Please have your coins ready.
- The fare...
- My wallet.
This is my wallet.
I might need a wallet.
- You should buy an elephant wallet.
- Yes.
My butt is getting hot.
It feels like a sauna.
- It's like a butt sauna.
- A butt sauna.
It'll come soon.
Two minutes to go.
Arriving in two minutes
I hope the bus looked like this.
It's not coming.
(Everyone got on their buses,
except them.)
Our bus is not coming.
A few moments later.
One hour later.
(They just keep waiting.)
- We're waiting and waiting.
- Look here.
- Try to look like you're forcing a smile.
- Okay.
Okay.
(Guys, don't do this.)
Is traveling always like this?
I completely checked out.
Are you losing your mind?
(A lot of them are losing their minds.)
What's wrong?
I want to go home.
We can't anyway!
We can't go home anyway!
- Hey!
- We can't go home anyway.
We can't go home!
Let me go ask.
Someone has been waiting
as long as we have.
She might be waiting for the same bus.
- Won Ji!
Hello.
Which bus are you waiting for?
No bus?
Why isn't it coming?
Oh, my.
- Traffic jam.
- Traffic jam?
All other buses came except ours.
Oh, we've never even seen that bus before.
- It's 1-92.
- It's good to see it.
So, I asked her.
She says it might be
because of traffic jams.
- But other buses had no problem.
- I know.
So I was thinking,
what if we all chip in for a taxi?
(That's a good idea.)
Let's just buy one less item.
Why didn't we think of that?
Let's call a taxi.
I'll do it.
Let's take a taxi.
What is she doing?
(Twerking for a taxi
in the middle of Bangkok)
- Let's go to our lucky place!
- Let's go.
I wonder how lucky we're going to get.
It better be some serious good luck.
It better be worth it when we get there.
(Setting off
while demanding some good luck)
(It's almost sunset now.)
Let's go.
- Okay!
- Let's go.
Taxis are indeed convenient!
- They're the best!
- Taxis!
Is it this way?
The map says...
It's over there.
We should cross.
- That does look like a theater.
- It looks so abandoned.
This neighborhood is really eerie.
I don't want to get closer.
I can't believe it.
(Rumbling)
(Suddenly, thunder rumbles.)
Thunder cracked.
This is not a set, right?
Did you prepare the weather too?
Is this an outdoor set?
This is "The Truman Show," isn't it?
Thunder rumbled.
I've never even watched a horror movie.
- I hate horror movies.
- Me too.
I even hate the posters.
I've never been
to a haunted house attraction either.
I've done that, at least.
Then does that make you less scared?
No, I'm still scared.
You've only done it.
I'm already scared.
The thunder really felt staged.
It came out of nowhere.
(Something feels off from the start.)
I can do it.
- Is that the building?
- I can do this.
(Despite their determination,)
(darkness soon fell
on their lucky place too.)
(Welcome.)
- This is the place.
- Come on.
- Here?
- Wait.
Yes.
It looks eerie.
- Is this the theater?
- Yes.
It does look like a haunted place.
Look how dark the entrance is.
Isn't it too dark?
Don't we need a flashlight?
(Noticing Harimu's face)
Harimu, are you all right?
I'm really not.
You look really scared.
Honestly, think about it.
If we see a ghost,
that means our show will go viral.
That's true.
If we don't, that's still good
because that means we're safe.
The lightning feels staged.
My goodness. All of a sudden...
Won Ji, I...
Lightning struck behind you.
I'm not scared of ghosts.
Ghosts, you die.
(Threatening ghosts that are already dead)
- Ghosts!
- Ghosts, come on!
- Come on, ghosts!
- I'm not scared.
She's doing that
because she's not the leader, right?
Why did I volunteer?
(Lightning flashes.)
(Using the lightning as a light source)
(At the start of a horror movie,
everyone is excited.)
It's so funny.
Harimu, you might be good
at fighting off ghosts.
Start!
- Ghosts, come on!
(Cheering)
Ghosts!
I...
I'm getting used to it.
- I find it fun. It's becoming part of me.
- We can do it!
Sian! You can do this!
- You volunteered!
- Right.
Ghosts might feel drained and run away.
Ghosts, you're out!
You're boring.
Seriously.
You suck.
- Suck?
- You really suck.
You're stinky.
(You hurt the ghosts' feelings.)
(Meanwhile)
(The abandoned theater got even darker.)
- Let's get going.
- Let's go.
- Can you do this?
- I can.
- We can do this.
- Just trust me!
- Let's go!
We'll catch ghosts!
- Link arms.
- Okay!
- Isn't it really creepy, though?
- It is.
It has a really bad vibe.
Why do they leave a place like this?
Why didn't they remodel the place?
Remodel the place?
Now that we're closer...
I can't. I don't want to.
The door is tightly shut.
It's so scary.
I got goosebumps.
Did you feel that?
Wait. What is that?
- What?
- Isn't that a suitcase?
Where's our suitcase?
I don't know!
I feel like there's something up there.
That yellow thing over there.
- I don't see it.
- Isn't that a suitcase?
- On our right.
- It is.
It doesn't have a sticker on it.
- I see it now.
- It scared me!
(That suitcase looks scarier here.)
- It looks so scary.
- My gosh! What do I do?
I'm so scared.
I'm sorry. I can't.
- Over there.
- There's nothing there.
What was that just now? A bird flew by.
It's okay.
- I see the suitcase.
- I've had it.
- Good idea. Grab some weapon.
- Yes.
But the sticker isn't on it.
Maybe it's a new suitcase?
Maybe it's not our original one.
Oh, no. I really don't want to go.
Do we have to go in here?
(Pitch-black darkness)
Who's there?
This is terrifying.
Terrifying.
No, I don't want to do this.
This is actually my first time.
Let's open the suitcase.
I think something's inside.
I don't think this is ours.
Yes.
Is this the reward
they were talking about?
Something before we go back?
I think we need to equip this.
What is it?
I think they want us to wear this
and film ourselves.
What?
(There's no one around but them.)
I don't like this!
Was that thunder and lightning?
What's over there?
This can't be real.
I'm going to wet myself.
There's nothing here.
- What's this?
- What's that?
I know what this is.
A noise meter?
It's a ghost detector.
If a ghost is nearby, it'll start moving.
Really?
- They have some kind of frequency.
- Wait, what's this?
What's this? Look.
What is that?
- What is it?
- I think we have to go somewhere.
I think we have to go watch a movie.
(A movie ticket dated today)
Abra-ca-Empty?
Abracadabra
Stop! Don't!
(Just a camera)
Stop that!
Don't.
(Harimu hits the deck mid-song)
Stop.
Twerk! Twerk!
(Might as well twerk)
That was so scary.
I almost had a heart attack.
There's this too.
A flashlight.
Four headlamps and one flashlight.
The person in the front can hold this.
(A must-have for the person in front)
I hate it!
(Silence)
Abracadabra!
- Okay.
- Let me go.
Come on.
We have to rely on each other.
This is what you call a girls' night.
I'll grab your shoulder from behind.
- Okay.
- I hope nothing grabs my ankles.
Can you just stick with me?
- Stick to you?
- Yes.
Hold me.
- Hold you?
- Yes.
That's cute.
I'm going in.
(Agh!)
Hold this and let's go.
- I'll hold it.
- You hold it.
I'll hold this...
- and grab you.
- If we don't make it out in 30 minutes,
- please save us!
- I can't keep up.
Someone has to hold you.
- Shall we?
- Okay.
Let's go.
- It's okay.
- It's okay, girls.
- This is nothing.
- It's going to be fine.
- It's nothing.
- Okay.
Do we go left or right?
Let's see. Left or right.
Do we have to go up the stairs?
It should be left, right?
(First, a quick peek to the left)
Here we go.
- Huh?
- This is so wrong.
(A dark and humid corridor)
What the hell?
Oh, come on.
(Slowly moving forward)
- Please.
- The windows are all broken.
I think they were praying here.
Please don't jump scare us.
I'm begging you.
Watch your step.
We can do this.
I really hate this.
Please... Twerk.
Twerk.
(I twerk when I'm scared.)
Wait. We're good.
- Can you please grab me here?
- Sure.
(The biggest scaredy-cat takes the lead.)
This is crazy.
It won't be dangerous.
It says to keep out.
Are we going in there?
Do we go over this?
(Dead end)
I don't think this is it.
- It's not?
- Something's closed over here.
Wow, I can't see anything up ahead.
This flashlight isn't that great.
(Can't see anything behind them)
Seriously?
- Oh, crap.
- This is really scary.
It's okay.
Be careful.
Please be careful.
Watch your step.
Look at the shattered glass.
- Who broke it?
- We're in trouble.
(Shattered mirror)
(Pause)
Oh, my.
- Wow.
- Is that a haechi?
What is that?
It's a toad.
(Who broke that?)
This is crazy. You must be joking.
Wow.
(Too scared to go in, just peeking)
This place is...
- Where do we go?
- What do we do?
We need some signs at least.
(Complete darkness)
- Why is this place so big?
- I think it's this way.
- Left?
- Let me head this way.
- I don't think it's upstairs.
- We can't go up the stairs.
(Heading to the big space on the left)
It's okay.
- Stay calm.
- We have four people.
Wow, it's here.
This is the place we saw in the photo.
This is it. That escalator is here.
The place we saw in the photo.
(The escalator they saw in the QR code)
(Singing)
What is it?
It's nothing.
Don't do that.
(It's just the staff.)
We are looking for our reward.
We came a long way.
(Forcing each step,
thinking about the reward)
Don't do that.
I'm pretty sure we have to go up.
We go up?
I think this is it.
Yes, this is what we saw in the photo.
Do we have to go up?
- We have...
- Are you sure this isn't going to break?
no choice.
Wow, look at all that dust.
Are you sure we can go up?
I'm so scared.
(It looks like it's never been used.)
Did someone send the dragon of fear?
Who sent us the dragon of fear?
- Hold on!
- What is it?
- Why?
- What is fear?
Fear...
is an illusion.
Fear is an illusion!
- Fear is an illusion!
(Dropping quotes to hide the fear)
It's all in my head!
- True.
- It's all in my head!
- It's just the dark.
- That's right.
We sleep in the dark.
- Oh, yes.
- Right?
Every day...
we have at least 8 hours of darkness.
- Yes.
- Let's go.
Pass me the flashlight.
Flashlight for the lead.
Let's go.
- Wow, there are dead feathers.
- Wow, look.
There are spiderwebs here.
- There are feathers everywhere.
- Wow, spiderwebs.
(Jingle)
What was that? Did you hear that?
I heard a jingling sound from above.
You heard that, right?
It sounded like a toad.
Like yesterday?
We heard toads yesterday.
- Yes.
- Watch your step.
Let's try not to freak out on the stairs.
- Yes.
- If we jump here, it's going to be bad.
(Jingle)
It's very...
- I knew it. It was a jingle!
- You're right.
- I heard it too.
- Yes.
- It jingled.
- But we're on the stairs!
Wasn't this supposed to be
a suitcase trip?
I know, right?
What do they think they're doing?
Why are there so many feathers?
Agh!
What?
We're still on the stairs!
The stairs!
A bird!
We made it!
- We came a long way.
- That's right.
- Totally.
But where's the reward?
What's that?
(Multiple doors with mirrors on them)
Let's go find out.
(Scouting the place)
- I think this will break if I step on it.
- This is crazy.
This is insane.
My underwear is soaked with sweat.
This really is insane.
Unbelievable.
(An insane situation)
- Where do we go now?
- This is beyond scary.
I think...
Shouldn't we use this ticket?
That's exactly what I was going to say.
I get it. Let's look for a box office.
I get it now.
Is the box office normally upstairs?
(Chaos)
Oh, come on!
What was it?
(Sian gets startled by the camera again.)
- Where's the theater?
- Hold on.
Hold on a second.
There was nothing there, right?
Please don't scream.
- My nose is sweating.
- I'm so scared.
I'm dripping in sweat.
Okay. Let's go again.
There was nothing there.
(Hands held tight)
- Calm down.
- Don't cry.
- There's nothing there.
- I think we have to go into the theater.
- No way.
No jump scares, please.
- You're the scariest right now.
- No one did anything.
You're our biggest fear, Sian.
It's true, Sian.
I'm so overwhelmed.
No one jump-scared us.
(Jingle)
You must be freaking kidding me.
(It's so scary a curse word slipped out.)
Do we have to go there?
(Where the jingle came from)
Do we have to follow the jingle?
- It came from there.
- I think so.
I think we'll have to go toward the sound.
Dang it!
(Jingle)
Stay back!
- Oh, come on!
- Wait.
(The fact is, no one went near them.)
Is there something there?
Look over there.
(They found the door
where the jingle came from.)
- Let's go over there.
- Why is it so close?
I'm pretty sure it's that room.
You're lying.
- I'm sweating.
- We have to go in there?
Seriously?
We have to cross that river?
(Crossing the hall to find the reward)
My feet are sweating.
- This is insane.
- It's crazy.
I don't think I can go in there.
I'm serious.
(Come in.)
(Turn)
(Glancing)
Crap.
I'm sweating like crazy.
Let's just use the flashlight
at the entrance.
(One step closer to the door)
Let's test the water.
- Come here.
- Dear God.
There's something written here.
It's not for us,
is it?
I'm sure it's not.
(Suspicious red writing)
The sound is coming from there.
And it's pissing me off.
It's so annoying.
Wait. Where do we head from here?
- So scary.
- Left?
What are we looking for?
- Let's just go in!
- My legs won't move.
Okay.
This place is crazy.
I've never seen anything like this.
(A pitch-black hallway)
It's going to jingle again soon.
Come here and hold my hand.
I'll hold your hand.
Yes, hold my hand.
Perfect.
It's so scary.
- There's nothing over here.
- Is this it?
- Wait. I'm so scared.
- Shh.
(Pause)
It's over there.
There.
(Where the jingle is coming from)
- It's open here.
- Why do I even have to do this?
I know, right?
- You hear that, right?
- Yes.
- I can hear the jingle.
- It's getting louder.
(Getting louder as they approach)
- I'm way too scared.
- There's nothing on the right.
- Nothing on the right or left, right?
- What's in front?
It's a theater.
Oh, the stairs go down.
Unbelievable.
What on earth is this?
It's complete darkness.
It's pitch black.
I'm usually terrified
of looking under chairs.
Seriously.
- Her accent is slipping out.
- Seriously.
I'm not kidding.
Don't do it.
- I'm dying of heat.
- Don't grab my ankle or anything.
I'm going to get mad. I'm going home.
I'm a travel YouTuber.
I'll straight-up buy a ticket and leave.
Just a little bit.
At least the sides look okay.
There's nothing there.
Nothing's going to fall from above, right?
(How did she know?)
(Terrified)
(The sisters immediately bolt.)
(Gabee turns around
and bursts out laughing.)
(Harimu freezes in place like a scorpion.)
(One by one, they return
to check on the scorpion.)
(They belatedly reach out to pet her.)
(Sweat glands back in overdrive)
- I'm scared.
- I'm sweating.
Look at all this sweat.
I guess it was just a wig.
Where did it come from?
I think there are seats upstairs too.
We totally overreacted.
- That was it?
- Yes.
- Let's put it on and keep moving.
- Okay.
Look at her. She's drenched in sweat.
(Putting on the wig
with pure determination)
I think you can pull this off.
(After one big jump scare,
she's dark and fearless.)
You're amazing.
- Did someone throw it?
- I don't know. It just fell.
(Heading back inside)
Don't do it.
- Seriously, don't.
- I said don't do it.
Please don't.
Don't do it.
Is there something in here?
How old are these chairs, anyway?
I'm actually fine with creepy things.
- It's being startled that I hate.
- I know. Just...
(Bump)
I just hate jump scares.
I'm not scared at all.
(The camera accidentally bumps into them.)
I don't like horror movies.
- I guess we should go downstairs, right?
- Okay.
(Clinging tightly
to each other's hands again)
- Why are there so many chairs?
- I know, right?
- This place must be huge.
- It had to be a massive theater.
Looks like it could seat 300 people.
Hold on.
- Why are there so many chairs?
- Wait.
Doesn't that look
like something black over there?
- Looks like only that spot is black.
- I think so too.
There's something over there.
- Is that the lucky item?
- Are my eyes playing tricks on me?
No, you're right. There's something black.
Let's do it this way.
(Checking both sides row by row
as they advance)
Next, row 2.
Row 2 is clear.
Okay.
- Row 3.
- Row 3 is clear, right?
- We got this.
- I'm sweating bullets.
(Slowly making their way down)
I don't think that's a person.
Then what is it?
That's...
- Your voice...
- Are you okay?
It looks like someone
hanging their head down.
I really can't go any further.
Inching closer row by row
makes it even creepier.
- I'll go.
- Okay.
I'm going.
That hair is really long.
It's just a wig.
It doesn't have a body.
If that weren't a wig,
I would've passed out.
We fell for it.
But I think we need to go over there.
- Near that head?
- Yes.
Don't you think there might be
a clue over there?
(Could the lucky item be inside the wig?)
I'm going.
(Won Ji cautiously approaches.)
Hey!
It's a balloon.
A balloon?
If we pop it, something has to be inside.
I'm scared of popping balloons.
(Pop)
There's nothing.
(Venting her anger after finding nothing)
At times like this,
we can't break formation.
- Is something written there?
- We need to stick together.
(Like a terrified bodyguard)
(Jingle)
(Not there.)
(The bell rings again.)
I hear a bell.
Behind us.
- Behind us?
- This way.
In front?
(Following the chime,
they venture deeper inside.)
This is the right way.
- Is this right?
- Yes.
Seriously, where is it?
We've come way too far in.
Getting back out is going to be a pain.
I'm sweating so much.
There's something here.
- It's a suitcase.
- A suitcase.
It's a suitcase.
This is seriously creepy.
I'll bring it over.
Good idea.
Rimu Queen, you can do it.
Why?
Did they give us another suitcase?
- It's a lucky suitcase, it says.
- Really?
For real?
Finally?
It's...
It's a bigger suitcase!
- It's much bigger.
- Great.
"This is your reward."
"Exchange your original suitcase
for this larger one."
Okay.
So we just take this with us now?
Is this bigger than ours?
- Way bigger.
- Right.
Thank goodness.
I have no idea where we are.
Let's get out.
We should go back.
It's scary.
(The bell rings even louder.)
(Pure panic)
(Ensuring the walk back isn't too quiet)
I can't lead,
but I can't be in the back either!
(Quickly rushing back toward the entrance)
Don't even try dropping anything.
I see right through you.
(Keeping their eyes glued to the ceiling)
This is seriously terrifying.
Yes, this is so scary.
(What on earth did she see?)
That's so creepy.
- Why?
- What's that?
(Won Ji suddenly completely freezes up.)
It's a real ghost.
It really is.
Did you see a ghost?
Let's go.
Hang in there till the end.
There are stairs here too.
Okay.
- It's raining.
- No way.
- This happened to me last time too.
Why does it always rain
right after we finish?
It's insane.
It always pours when we're done.
I'm completely drained.
How can someone
just stand there alone like that?
Someone was up on the balcony.
They were just standing there
staring blankly.
That was one of the crew, right?
- Wait, they're not there?
- Are they gone now?
(The expressionless figure
they all supposedly saw)
Wasn't that a producer?
(The crew couldn't have
accessed that area.)
Wait, so it really was a ghost?
When we were leaving the theater,
I said I was scared, and they just
stood there staring like this.
- Yes, with zero expression.
- Completely blank.
- Really?
- Yes.
(The footage shows nothing
at that moment.)
Stop lying. I saw it too.
(A darkened face)
I was sweating so much.
I keep thinking about it.
I was walking while holding
Harimu's hand so tightly.
Then the second the wig dropped,
I let go of her hand and flew backward.
I had no clue what was happening.
(The fastest movement
since arriving in Thailand)
And then Hye Rim was
in this full scorpion pose.
She was literally like this.
(Transformed into a scorpion)
That's my desperate survival pose.
I was like this.
- Exactly like that.
- She really was.
It's a desperate pose for survival.
It was so funny.
We can use this tomorrow.
I didn't realize
there'd be such a difference.
There really is a huge difference.
There really is.
Because we trusted each other,
we were able to pull this off.
Our teamwork was great.
High five.
We beat the ghost.
Get out of here, ghost!
We got a big suitcase.
I'm so happy.
We have way more room now.
(The ghost detector suddenly goes wild.)
The light turned red.
Let me out.
Let's pack up and go.
(Fleeing the scene)
- Let's get out before it attaches to us.
- Let's go.
- Don't attach to us.
- Don't follow us.
- Let me go get some salt.
- Good idea.
(The abandoned theater
falls silent once again.)
(What did they actually see that night?)
(Heading back to the lodge
before the night grows deeper)
I seriously need to use the bathroom.
(B-lining straight for the bathroom
upon arrival)
(Just how urgent was it?)
I'm dying.
Oh, I'm dying.
I should've used this
to beat up the ghost.
(Whack)
(Now that it's over,
her confidence is back.)
(Rejoining the crew completely refreshed)
I feel so much better.
Laundry time.
These are towels, so take one each.
And this one is Harimu's.
(Elephant pants returning
to their rightful owner)
The red ones.
There's a hole right here.
It's sexy.
Mine got a hole in them too.
Sexy.
I had no idea mine ended up like this.
Mine did too.
I feel like I sweated out two kilos today.
- Let's meet up after showering.
- Sounds good.
Okay.
(Gabee finishes showering first)
(Rummaging around)
Yesterday,
I felt bad about the Secret Santa gift
I gave you.
Did you buy something else?
What's that?
You said you wanted a headscarf.
When did you buy this?
(Before leaving for the lucky spot)
Thank you.
I feel like I didn't do
Secret Santa properly.
So I bought something for Won Ji.
This looks perfect for her.
- It looks so cute.
- This is awesome.
(Cuteness score up)
I'm going to put this on tomorrow.
Right away.
It just screamed Won Ji.
I'm wearing it tomorrow.
Gabee's so considerate.
Yes.
Are you still doing
your Secret Santa stuff?
This is so wholesome.
It looks perfect for you.
(Appreciating)
Thanks so much.
You're welcome.
The bandana is so pretty.
It was a good buy.
I'm going to unbox my gift too.
It's just so cute.
(Muhaha)
Elephants are so cute.
(Elephant-obsessed)
The colors are just so pretty.
I just think the blue one is so pretty.
(Relaxing after a shower)
(After recuperating)
That's cute.
Toadie, golden toadie.
You lost three today?
Your nails?
They're falling off one by one.
Harimu's pedicures are cute too.
(Demure)
By the way,
the person in the projection room...
wasn't our producer.
No way.
(Hot topic: the ghost's identity)
But wait.
I thought it was him over there.
- Right.
- Wasn't it you?
It really wasn't you?
If it really wasn't him...
- It really wasn't you?
- No way.
I thought you were the person
in the second-floor projection room.
This is so chilling. For real?
All four of us saw it.
It was definitely a person, not a ghost.
Come on, stop messing with us.
Won Ji, you saw it, right?
Was there even a projection room?
I guess so, since it was a theater.
"I guess so, since it was a theater."
I love answers like that.
So nobody went to the projection room?
I think they're telling the truth.
Really?
It really wasn't you guys?
I don't think I'm sleeping tonight.
Is that for real?
(Did we see a ghost?)
I'm sleeping in Gabee's bed tonight.
Can you wash your hair first, Won Ji?
(Can you wash your hair?)
(Hair smell scarier than a ghost)
It was so hard to get through that door.
Remember the wig dropping down on us?
And on the way back, there was a ghost.
- Wig ghost.
- Also, scorpion.
(Harimu: dancer and scorpion)
That pose just comes out
when I'm at death's door.
You mean when you're scared?
Have you ever almost died?
When did you do the scorpion pose?
Whenever I was scared.
(Scorpion mode)
(Touched)
We can see inside your shorts.
(Spicy underwear reveal)
But nobody else saw it.
I thought I might share it.
(Stronger bond forged)
But we really need some salt.
There definitely is a ghost.
Definitely there is.
(Clang)
(Rushing in)
(Screaming)
I can't!
What, what is it?
(Huddled)
What? Who was that?
Did someone go upstairs?
There's someone else here?
This is so chilling.
Stop messing with me.
That must have been the boiler.
No, it sounded like the toad instrument.
No, it sounded like a bell.
I thought it sounded like this.
(Slithering)
Yes, it sounded like this.
No, it was a bell.
I thought someone was going upstairs?
But there's nothing on the third floor.
I was just there.
How are we sleeping tonight?
Let's go.
Where?
- Upstairs.
- Good luck.
Be the first, Gabee.
Won Ji!
Come on, leader.
(Not listening)
Let me go.
I don't think there's anything.
It's so silly how we're all going.
Gabee, are you trying
to sneak to the back?
(Going to the back)
Let's have our scorpion lead the way.
Okay.
It was a bell.
I definitely heard a bell.
I thought it was a person going like this.
(Cracking up)
This is scary, just this.
(The scorpion crawls up.)
(Standing still)
Won Ji, why aren't you joining us?
(Howling)
Is anybody on the second floor?
(Come here, Won Ji.)
I think something is
in Gabee and Won Ji's room.
No way.
There's something up there.
I found this.
It's the QR code.
You found something.
(Scorpion express)
Let me scan the QR code.
Is that our plan for tomorrow?
I think so.
What?
What is it, Won Ji?
Can we be surprised together?
Okay.
Our second stop
for this one-suitcase trip is...
the mountain city of...
Chiang Mai.
(Shining 24 and 7 from day to night)
(The city of artists)
(Filled with colorful and unique charm)
(The jewel of Northern Thailand)
(Chiang Mai)
What is it?
I'm getting annoyed.
That's not good.
Don't annoy her. I hate you.
"For each gram you shed,
we'll offer extra funds."
They can't do this
after giving us a bigger bag.
I thought we had good fortune.
(Would this be good fortune?)
I think they're giving us a place to stay.
- Nice.
- Wait.
Sian, you'll like this.
What is it?
They have elephants there.
Oh!
(Squealing)
Really?
Our place is called
Chiang Mai Elephant something.
Maybe we get to feed the elephants.
It says, "a fantastic place
where you can play with elephants."
I never thought
we'd get to see an elephant.
This is so cool.
I never expected this.
I'm going to put him on my shoulder.
I'll put one on each side.
I'll also wear an elephant shirt...
and elephant shorts.
You have elephant shorts?
Mine are still intact.
(Certified elephant enthusiast)
They all told me
about how they want to see elephants.
Look, an elephant.
- They've never seen one before.
- Right.
Never.
- You've seen one before, Won Ji?
- Yes, I have.
I never touched one, though.
- I'm so happy right now.
- Me too.
Me too.
(Shake it if you love elephants.)
(Cheering)
(So happy just because of the elephant)
Are we going to shoot Reels
with the elephants?
- I'm in.
- Good.
Come on.
They're just so cute. I'm so excited.
I want to go to bed already.
Wait, we should pack first.
Our bag's over here.
Let's go.
(The new, bigger bag arrives.)
Okay, let's get packing.
We'll bring our stuff down.
(Sian and Harimu get their luggage.)
Let me put everything
in the elephant bag Harimu gave me.
Sian, do you have a spare elephant shirt?
- Do you want to borrow one?
- Can I?
Of course.
(Sharing clothes naturally)
I've never traveled this light before.
I think we can let go
of that curling iron.
Do you need it?
I don't know.
I'll leave the discussion
up to the curling iron users.
I'll talk to them about it.
Feel free to discuss it among yourselves.
About the curling iron...
Do you need it?
- I don't think so.
- Okay.
I can let it go.
What about the beauty device?
You're letting a lot of things go.
(Detaching after just 3 days)
- Off goes the beauty device.
- I just don't have time.
(Curling iron and beauty device out)
Where's my toad?
A lot of things are getting shed.
(In curling iron
and beauty device's place,)
Three elephants, please.
(goes toad and elephant.)
We have to pack the shoes too.
Right.
The slippers.
Let me try.
You think they'll fit?
We have more than we thought.
(The bigger suitcase is soon full.)
Okay.
(Heavy)
It's definitely bigger.
(Pressing)
I can't close it.
(Full of greed)
Let's open it back up.
Let's take the slippers out.
We'll carry them to the car.
They're light, but bulky.
I don't like it.
This should be enough.
Okay.
I think we can close it.
(Successfully closed)
Okay.
Okay, let's get the scale.
(Bringing out the scale)
For every 100 grams we shed...
Wait, they'll give us 10 dollars.
(Every 100 gs are 10 dollars less.)
But if we go over, we have to pay a fine.
Can you try lifting it?
Let my brain calculate.
(Drumroll)
Wow.
I think this is over 20 kg.
Really?
Right.
We should take some out.
We have to. Because...
- Okay.
- The stakes are too high.
It's 10 dollars per 100 g.
(Not ready to lose even a cent)
Let's take out some non-essentials.
Sian, I think yours is a bit too big.
It is kind of big.
It's heavy too.
But I just have one.
(Thick)
What's in here?
It's big.
Let me just take out the heaviest thing.
This is super heavy.
These pants are heavy.
(Leopard print pants out)
What about this?
Oh, that one?
(Next candidate: wedding dress)
I don't think that one's too heavy.
Let's take this out.
Take it out?
- I don't think we'll wear it.
- You're not going to wear it?
Well.
Let's take it out.
You're taking it out
because you don't want to wear it, right?
How did you know?
Then I'm putting it back in.
Do you have anything you can wear?
The hair straightener is in there.
I took one out earlier,
but there's another one inside.
What is this? My last worldly possession?
Let's just put it in for now.
(We'll let this one slide
if you love it that much.)
All right.
What's this?
My clothes.
Hold on.
I think there's something in here.
- Show me.
- It's just clothes.
- What's in there?
- Take out whatever you can.
But...
These pants are heavy.
Aren't you going to wear them tomorrow?
- These are a bit heavy.
- Right.
Then I should set aside
what I'm going to wear tomorrow too.
I'm going to wear this tomorrow.
(Declaring that pajamas count
as getting dressed up)
If it's going to be too heavy,
I should wear the pants.
I should wear this tomorrow.
- It's much lighter now, right?
- It went down a lot.
It's totally flat now.
We really took out a lot.
This is so easy.
If we can get it down to about 19 kg,
we'll get 100 dollars.
Let me try lifting it.
I think it's about 18 kg.
Maybe 18.5 kg?
(Staring)
But you can't take this out, Sian.
Why did you take this out?
I have the bag Hye Rim bought me
yesterday.
Are you okay with this?
Hold on. I'll just check what's in there.
You don't need the sunglasses?
That was close.
My Gongjindan was in here.
- Gongjindan.
- Passport.
- That's precious.
You were going to throw your passport out?
You almost couldn't go back to Korea.
You really have to keep
an eye on these kids.
I need looking after.
Okay, let me go.
(Time to weigh the suitcase)
(Celebrating prematurely)
(Even the expanded suitcase
is packed to the brim.)
Let's see!
Hold on.
(The suitcase weighs 19.65 kg.)
(Successfully shedding 350 g)
(The helicopter celebration)
(It catches on.)
Give me my money.
"You received 235 dollars per person..."
- "for each day of the trip."
- Nice!
Because of this?
If the suitcase got bigger
but weighs less,
that means we really did clear things out.
Did we really pack everything?
- I'm getting nervous.
- It does feel a little suspicious.
That's true.
Still, we got our spending money.
Let's sleep.
- Elephants.
I can sleep with Gabee tonight.
Let's all sleep together tonight.
It's our last night in Bangkok.
- Sure.
- I love it.
Come down to this floor.
- Come down to this floor.
- I'm scared.
(Their final night in Bangkok
ends on a high note.)
Next, we're heading to Chiang Mai.
(To the second terrain, Chiang Mai)
Let's go.
(Maximum energy from the start)
(And the madness catches on.)
Honey. Babe.
(Don't leave me out.)
(The extroverts are having
the time of their lives.)
(Meanwhile, the introvert is slowly
running out of battery.)
Bring it up.
- Bring it up.
(You're too close.)
(Will she be able to adjust today?)
There are the elephants.
Wow.
(The long-awaited encounter
with elephants)
This is amazing.
(Sian's dream comes true?)
(Starting with an up-close view
of an elephant feast)
When else would we ever get
to go for a walk with an elephant?
Look at that.
This is insane.
It feels so good.
(Kissing)
It really feels like you're connecting.
One more.
Hey, you're something else.
What's wrong with you?
That's not cool.
- What are you doing?
- It fell!
(Their affection grows more intense.)
(Looks like a fairy tale from afar,
but pure chaos up close)
It feels like a fairy tale.
I really can't handle this.
It's so cute.
But I'm scared.
(Will the romance last until the end?)
(Subtitles are provided by KOCOWA.)